Kim M. Heimann



Quality Assurance Analyst in St. Louis, MO

I oversee and ensure a high and consistent quality of work. As a team member, I work to troubleshoot and efficiently solve problems while holding myself and others to high administrative standards. And most notably, I have decades of experience, necessitating adaptation to an ever-changing work environment and software upgrades.

PHONE 314-420-7873 | **EMAIL** heimannk549@gmail.com

GITHUB https://github.com/heimannkim

LINKEDIN https://www.linkedin.com/in/kim-heimann-26a60690/

PROJECT EXPERIENCE

Shopping List — Shared by shoppers within a group

- Shoppers within a specified group can add, edit, or delete items in a shopping list
- Synchronized list for reference when it's time to shop
- Plan is to eventually convert for iPhone/Android use

WORK EXPERIENCE

IS Quality Assurance Analyst — Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis, MO (Shared Billing and Collection Services)

January 2008 - Present

- Monitor the Information Systems internal staff and vendors to ensure adherence to IT Audit Controls
- Approve and move software configuration changes made in the test system to the production system
- Responsible for ensuring system integrity and compliance with University Policies
- Liaison between West (ClientTell) and physician offices for appointment reminder software. Responsible for transition from West (ClientTell) to Relatient on GE system
- Assumed Help Desk duties during transition from GE system to Epic system

Production Supervisor — Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis, MO (Shared Billing and Collection Services)

September 1995 - December 2007

- Supervise staff responsible for printing claims, statements, reports, etc. in the production environment
- Planning, execution and troubleshooting for automated production processes (claims, statements, reporting, etc.)
- Coordinate inventory control to maintain volume of all necessary forms for operational reliability

Computer Operator III — Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis, MO (Shared Billing and Collection Services)

December 1994 - August 1995

Supervise staff responsible for printing claims, statements, reports,
etc. in the production environment

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

- Java
- Python
- HTML5/CSS3

FRAMEWORKS

- Hibernate
- Spring
- Flask

TEMPLATE ENGINES

- Thymeleaf
- · Jinja2

DATABASES

- MySQL
- SQLAlchemy

MICROSOFT

- Excel
- Outlook
- PowerPoint
- Word

GE CENTRICITY BUSINESS SOFTWARE

- Auto-transfers
- Auto-writeoffs
- BAR Form letters
- Batch maintenance
- Claims

- Planning, execution and troubleshooting for automated production processes (claims, statements, reporting, etc.)
- Coordinate inventory control to maintain volume of all necessary forms for operational reliability

Computer Operations Supervisor — Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis, MO (Consortium Computing Facilities)

September 1991 - November 1994

- Supervise staff responsible for printing claims, statements, reports, etc. in the production environment
- Planning, execution and troubleshooting for production processes (claims, statements, reporting, etc.)
- Coordinate inventory control to maintain volume of all necessary forms for operational reliability

Systems Operator — Washington University School of Medicine in St. Louis, MO (Consortium Computing Facilities)

April 1989 - August 1991

- Planning, execution and troubleshooting for production processes (claims, statements, reporting, etc.)
- Coordinate inventory control to maintain volume of all necessary forms for operational reliability

Computer Operator/Lab Instructor — Sanford-Brown Business College in St. Louis, MO

March 1983 - April 1989

- Planning, execution and troubleshooting for production processes (attendance, grades, schedules, reporting, etc.)
- Coordinate inventory control to maintain volume of all necessary forms for operational reliability
- Help students in computer lab environment (COBOL, BASIC, RPG, etc.)

EDUCATION

CoderGirl, SQL Servers and Databases — In Progress **LaunchCode,** LC101 Programming Course — 2019

Sanford-Brown Business College, AA in Systems Analysis — 1982

processing

- Dictionary maintenance
- Move TUUs (production changes)
- Reporting queries and downloads
- Statement processing
- TES evaluations and extractions
- Wipe clean and recreate test environment

VENDOR SOFTWARE

- Apex Revenue Tech. (statement)
- ClientTell (appointment reminder)
- Diamond HealthCare (statement)
- Relatient (appointment reminder)